<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tree Zero</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="first_number">0</string>
    <string name="submit_binary">111101 111111</string>
    <string name="unknownError">Something went wrong</string>
    <string name="yes">yes</string>
    <string name="no">no</string>
    <string name="buy">Are you sure you want to purchase this buster?</string>
    <string name="confirmation">Confirmation</string>
    <string name="noMoneyNoHoney">not enough numbers, click more</string>
    <string name="confirm">11011111101011</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="goal">1101000110010111011001110000</string>
    <string name="end">You saved a tree</string>
    <string name="yourTime">Congratulations, you have saved the tree.\nYou spend </string>
    <string name="endDescription"> fFor this time you could save some tress in real life</string>
    <string name="goalDescription"> In this game you need to save a digital tree from dying.\n\nTo save this tree you need to collect all binary numbers that are lost in decimals.\n\nList of all binary numbers contain 40 groups of 25 numbers, when you collect a group you make one digital leaf alive.\n\nEach leaf will help you to gain clicks when you are not in the app by adding numbers each minute.\n\nIn the shop you can buy busters to increase or decrease clicker.\n\nHelp to save this tree</string>
    <string name="clickerDescription"> Hello digital seeker, this is a clicker where you need to save a digital tree.\n\nTo save this tree you need to collect all binary numbers that are lost in decimals.\n\nList of all binary numbers contain 40 groups of 25 numbers, when you collect a group you make one digital leaf alive.\n\nThis is a clicker screen, here you can find this binary numbers, when you find one click 111101 111111 button to confirm it to the lost numbers list. The bottom navigation will help you to reach desired screen just tap on icon you want.</string>
    <string name="shopDescription">This is a shop screen, here you can find busters that increase your tap value with "x" to find desirable number faster and decrease your click with "d" to come back to some value if you missed one.</string>
    <string name="binsDescription">This is a list if 40 groups of lost binary numbers, each group contain 25 lost numbers. When you collect all numbers in a group one digital leaf will be saved and will help you by adding 1 in a minute when you are not in the app. you can click each group to look what numbers you need to find.</string>
    <string name="treeDescription">This is a screen with a digital tree you need to save. Now all leafs are empty and you need to collect all lost binary numbers to make them alive. Each leaf will help you gain clicks when you are not in the app.</string>
    <string name="tree">Tree</string>
    <string name="shop">Shop</string>
    <string name="clicker">Clicker</string>
    <string name="numbers">List</string>
</resources>